A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
What's going to happen next?
At this point, who knows?
But we can be sure about one thing at least.
With the Kishin around, the whole world will be buried in madness.
Did Medusa really believe she'd be able to beat such an opponent?
Which do you mean? The Kishin or the Grim Reaper?
Whichever. It seems impossible either way.
I wish I knew what was going on in there.
Blackstar, are you ready for this?
We've got to find a way to hold him back.
Hold him back? Give me a break.
I don't know about you, but I got bigger plans than that.
I'm gonna kill this guy!
Maka?
Is it you?
Yeah.
Who are you expecting?
It's Sol.
I'm falling down to my shadow
I'm falling down to my breath
Don't scare me
I'm falling down to my eyes
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby
Little dark unhappy
I'm falling down to my eyes
冗談
We'll be right back.
It is you. I'm so relieved.
This isn't over, though.
I'm locked in this room.
I relied too much on the black blood.
And because of that, most of my soul has been consumed by its insanity.
Yeah, I know. That's why I'm here to get you.
Hurry up. We need to get out of this room.
We can't.
The door's gone. It disappeared behind you as soon as you walked in.
Is there another way?
If I knew that, do you think I'd still be hanging around?
Yeah, okay. You've got a good point.
Window?
None at all.
We could break through the wall.
Nope.
Or rip up the floor and dig a tunnel.
No way.
Then we'll never get out of here.
Actually, there is a way.
Really?
The one and only way out of here.
Sink or swim.
The men who transcend the gods?
Death cannon.
Thanks for the excellent massage. It was quite rejuvenating.
I thought I was never going to get that crick out of my neck.
We need to do something. We're losing ground quickly.
Losing ground? But that implies you've gained some to begin with.
When you're up against a power as strong as mine is, it's not a question of gaining ground or making progress.
It's a question of staying alive.
Unfortunately for you, that particular question isn't going to have a pleasant answer.
You're right. With the level of attack we're using now, we're hard-pressed to even put a dent in you.
In which case, we're just going to have to attack you even harder, aren't we?
Dad.
I'm sorry. I didn't understand what you were doing.
I doubted you in every move you made.
Then the Kishin defeated you.
And it's all my fault.
Pathetic.
Useless.
I don't deserve to be his son.
I wish...
I wish I trusted him.
Things would be different now.
I failed my father.
Maybe I don't have what it takes to do this.
But...
I could try.
Clear me now, Asherah.
Die in the name of the Grim Reaper.
Liz, Patty, ready?
Yeah!
Let's go, Sauron!
His soul is so strong.
Blackstar, follow my lead now.
I'll need some backup.
That's a low move, kid!
No way!
Stealing my spotlight at a time like this?
We don't have time to fool around.
Can't you see that right now, all that matters is destroying him?
I need you to hold him back until I'm ready.
What will you do?
This next shot.
I'm giving it all I have.
There will be no second chances.
Back me up.
Hell no!
What?
That plan doesn't work for me.
First, I'll charge right at him.
Then you can join the fight and back me up when you're ready.
Oh, Blackstar?
I'm the star of this show till it's over.
Have it your way.
Have it.
Ah!
K…
Kid!
A way out?
Great.
So what should we do?
Is that it?
A box?
Looks like it's locked.
What the?
Careful. Go easy on that, okay?
You gotta be gentle. It's my courage that's locked up in there.
Liar!
It isn't my courage in here.
Do you hear me, Maka?
It's me locked inside.
Don't you get it?
Maka, look, I'm down here.
I'm inside the box.
This is all because of the black blood.
I used it too much, and now my courage is trapped inside that box.
That's why we need to open it, so we can both get out of this room.
He's lying, Maka.
It's me. I sealed myself in here before the black blood could take over.
If you open the box, my soul will be consumed by the black blood.
I tried everything I could possibly think of, but nothing I did would open it.
He only wants you to open it for him so he can get in here and devour what's left of me.
Please see that. It isn't me out there. It's the demon.
Please, Maka. Maka!
The thing is, I'm pretty sure you're the only one who can get it open.
Yeah? I open this, and then you'll be able to get out?
Yeah, exactly. Just look. The key is in your hand.
You idiot! Don't listen to him! Do not open it!
You know that isn't me, Maka!
Kid.
Damn you!
Uh-uh-uh. You blame me for this? That's not fair.
I don't recall inviting you to follow me in here. That choice was yours.
Kid, what the heck's going on here? I've never seen your soul do something like that before.
I have no idea what's happening, but it sure is cool, I say!
Whatever it is, we better think of something to do now.
Huh? What's that?
The lines of Son Tzu.
I remember you now. You're the Grim Reaper's little son, aren't you?
Excellent. I can deal with you the same way I dealt with your father.
You've got the wrong target.
You shouldn't underestimate me. I'm the one who's going to destroy you, not him.
Take your eyes off me for a second, and it'll be the last thing you do.
Shut up, Exit.
Didn't I tell you? Don't take your eyes off me!
Black Star, big win!
Where are you looking? I'm here!
Nope, over here! Here!
Right here, you slowpoke!
Stop it right now!
The real one is...
Right here!
I've got you that time.
Yahoo!
What?
I warned you, didn't I?
I'm the one who's going to destroy you!
Now, kid! Fire away!
Hey, look at the strikes in his hand!
They're all connecting!
Resonance rate is at 2,000%? Impossible!
And the noise level is at zero!
Feedback complete. We're ready to fire.
We're ready to fire.
Let's go!
Woohoo! Woohoo!
We did it! We got the keyshin, Patty!
Woohoo!
What?
That was one hell of a shot.
But what happened to Kid?
It's no big deal. This is Kid we're talking about.
It'll take more than that to kill him.
Black Star?
Oh, no.
Come on.
Don't get so upset, Tsubaki.
If he's back, that can only mean one thing.
I knew it.
Today's the day I'm going to fulfill my destiny and surpass God.
Any movement down there?
Something must have happened.
There's a crack in the Grim Reaper's mask that wasn't there before.
Are you all right, Death Scythe?
Eh, could be a lot worse.
Can't you use your clairvoyance to see what's going on with the students and the keyshin inside the barrier?
I can't.
Not without a pre-established link to at least one of them.
Then for all we know, the battle could already be over.
Maybe they beat it.
Fool!
Nothing has been decided yet.
The battle's still going on.
What?
Are you sure about that?
Fool!
Of course I am.
Does that mean you can see what's going on inside?
Fool!
Silence!
I require a cup of tea before I deign to answer that.
Um, how about coffee instead?
Fool!
I said tea, and I mean tea.
This guy.
Hey, everybody.
What's all the commotion?
Stein, when did you get back here?
Why, did you miss me?
I guess I should apologize for causing so much trouble.
A little late for that.
This is serious.
Maka, Blackstar, and Kid are all inside that barrier, fighting the keyshin as we speak.
Maka.
Then it's up to her, to Maka.
We were right about it coming down to Genie Hunter.
Her mother's technique.
Maka's Genie Hunter.
Well?
Open it.
Go on.
Do it now.
Hurry up.
Don't do it!
Don't open the box!
What are you doing?
Open it, and we can go.
Sure.
But first, tell me something.
Pathetic!
If you're not gonna open it, I will.
I'm not giving you the key.
What?
Now.
Tell me who you are.
Maka.
What are you talking about?
You know me.
You're not Sol.
Shut up!
Of course I am.
Just look at me!
Liar!
Sol would never ask me for something like this.
I'm asking because there's no other way.
Okay.
Tell me why you closed the door.
The real Sol would never have closed it.
Not if it would trap me, too.
He would have told me to turn back.
I know my partner.
And you're not him.
Yes.
Nice one, Maka.
You're not an idiot.
Yeah, you're right.
Well, half right, at least.
I'm not the Sol you knew.
It's you.
Yes.
I may not look like your good friend, Sol, but I assure you I'm a genuine Sol eater.
And I am a part of Sol as well.
Just as he, too, is a part of me.
Sol and I work together combined in a single body.
We're partners, he and I, the kind that can't be separated no matter what.
That's why I say you're only half right.
I am Sol, but at the same time, I'm not.
It's complicated, I know.
I hope I'm not confusing you.
So the real Sol is inside this box.
Yes, that's correct.
Funny, isn't it?
Who would think such a small box could hold all his arrogance?
But no matter.
I don't need him anymore.
My plan is very nearly complete.
The world is nearly mine now.
I can almost taste my success.
You're the only thing standing in my way.
But not for too much longer.
You are going to do what I say.
Do it!
Refusing to open the box won't help anything.
If you don't unlock it, you'll have the pleasure of watching while Sol and I die.
So you have two choices.
Keep the box closed and kill me along with your dear friend.
Or open it and meet a new Sol.
One who's been consumed by the madness of the black blood.
Which will it be?
Sol is actually in here, though, right?
He absolutely is.
Right.
Then I'll open it.
I have to.
You what?
Are you the crazy one?
Haven't you heard a thing he said?
That's the right decision.
I knew you weren't the type of girl who would abandon her partner.
Now, go ahead.
Go on and open it.
Yes, I will.
But I won't let the insanity take Sol.
I'll save him.
I swear it!
I'm coming, Sol!
I'll save you.
You're right.
So...
I'm here!
Maka!
What happened?
Impossible.
You are the biggest moron, Maka.
Such an idiot.
But then, of course, that's what makes you the coolest partner a weapon could have.
Damn.
After everything I've done, I'm stuck back here again.
What are you getting so worked up about, little guy?
Little guy?
Pathetic.
You're getting rid of me, aren't you?
How could I do something like that?
You're still a part of me, after all.
And so...
I'll have to accept you.
We made it back.
Yeah, thanks to you we did.
Where did Kid and Blackstar go?
Kid!
Blackstar!
There's no reason to be surprised.
As expected, I am the one still standing.
They are the ones who fell before me, like insects.
You're fools if you expected some other outcome than this.
Welcome to harsh reality, children.
There are no surprises here, and no uncertainty.
Also...
There is no fear.
American history wird sino going shorten-
Those times we regimens through the Cashỷ Garden
Are all of our Misamyons.
The first time out.
We spend our time in our жизни on Blood Festival.
In the blood flow, we revenues.
We burn ourselves in the blood flow, which is necessary to serve us.
And the ones that make Him spill since its mercy,
We won't lose sight.
There was no peace, because it'sbuying measure there,
The more that's worth your enemy go,
XOVI
On the final episode of Soul Eater, the word is bravery.
Watch it, or I'll take your soul.